

TA QUANG HIEP

e: contact@henry9.com

p: (+84) 98 456 0269

a: Hanoi, Vietnam

dob: Apr 29, 1994

n: Vietnamese

g: Male

henry9.com

f / hiepta29

🛭 @henry9_

PROFILE



Web designer and front-end developer with 3+ year experience of building pixel perfect websites. Flexible in fast-faced, high pressure working environment; delivered efficient, high-quality works and ensured compliance with requirements and best practices. Focused on helping agile teams with UI development for large scale websites or client-side web apps.

WORK EXPERIENCE



ISHOPGO

WEB DESIGNER, FRONT-END DEVELOPER | JUN 2017 - OCT 2018

- Lead designer on Website Design. Comprehensively redesigned and maintained company websites and admin dashboards to improve user experiences. Transitioned imported CSS to preprocessed SASS.
- Collaborated with project managers, designers and customers to develop websites, landing pages.
 Validated sites by testing JS, CSS and HTML5 to ensure cross-platform compatibility.

EZ4HOME

CO-FOUNDER | FRONT-END DEVELOPER | OCT 2014 - APR 2017

- Connected with venture capitals for funding. Represented for the team to participate in multiple startup contests in order to call for investment.
- Developed designs & templates with a focus on UX, usability and marketing strategy for website, interactive demos, PowerPoint presentations and email marketing campaigns.
- Designed mobile application UI prototype for project, assisted other designers, architects and marketing team with various aspects of platform needed.

HENRY9

UI DESIGNER AND FRONT-END DEVELOPER | 2013 - PRESENT

Worked with individual clients, digital agencies, startups, and companies on projects ranging from UI design, front-end maintenance, WordPress theme development, and more.

MediWhite

· VIJA Link

· Autism 365

iTro

• Fitme

· Banyan Restaurant

iCheck

GCI Vietnam

IQoptions

EDUCATION



UNIVERSITY OF ENGINEERING & TECHNOLOGY - VNU

2012 - 2017

Graduated with bachelor's degree in Computer Science.

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND UI DESIGN - BACH KHOA APTECH

2013

Solid understanding of Website and Application design principles.

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE



PROFESSIONAL SKILLSETS

- W3C Validated HTML
- CSS3 with BEM/SMACSS via Sass/Less
- JavaScript (jQuery, Ajax, JSON)

WORKING KNOWLEDGE

- Strongly understand of responsive design, web animation and user experience optimization.
- Build & custom high-quality cross-browser templates from design or mockup.
- Familiar with Bootstrap 3/4, Foundation and Sass with Compass.
- Work with WordPress.
- Recently been learning React.

TOOLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- GitHub / Bitbucket
- Atom / Sublime Text

ACHIEVEMENTS & RECOGNITIONS



- Top 12 Tech startups & Young entrepreneurs at APEC SME O2O Forum II
 Ez4home | Lima, Peru Oct 2016
- Top 5 Finalists at Viet Challenge Global Entrepreneurship Competition
 Ez4home | Boston, US Apr 2016
- Top 10 Startups at Vietnam Silicon Valley Accelerator

Ez4home | Hanoi, Vietnam – Oct 2014

• 2nd Prize at Samsung App Contest

Push Up (Android App) | Team of 3 | Hanoi, Vietnam - 2015

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Languages: Vietnamese as mother tongue, also have good English communication skill (C1 certificate by VNU).
- Personal interests: play sport such as badminton, volleyball or football, gym, other teamwork physical activities
 and travelling. Also love dogs and taking good care of them.
- Based in Hanoi, Vietnam and looking forward to growing personally and professionally anywhere, want to be involved in projects that I can be proud of, join amazing teams and advance my development career.